<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on ze sheng</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on ze sheng</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright/><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zes1092.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>finger me</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/finger-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/finger-me/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m turning 19 this summer. I&amp;rsquo;m at the age where you stop living in your own personal movie starring you. Reality is too much to pretend like everyone gets a happy ending. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how distraction is necessary doing mindless activities like shopping and partying will keep you sane a little bit longer. 16 year old fake deep me would look at people in the mall like look at all these NPC.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m turning 19 this summer. I&rsquo;m at the age where you stop living in your own personal movie starring you. Reality is too much to pretend like everyone gets a happy ending. I&rsquo;ve learned how <strong>distraction is necessary</strong> doing mindless activities like shopping and partying will keep you sane a little bit longer. 16 year old fake deep me would look at people in the mall like look at all these NPC. I looked down at people numbing themselves with plastic because they didn&rsquo;t realise how pointless it was. Now I&rsquo;m like everyone knows we&rsquo;re all just trying to distract ourselves for a bit because life sucks and its draining. I used to be entitled thinking that I was unique for overthinking every situation all the time like life always had to be filled with act 3 movie scenes with dramatic realisations but you can&rsquo;t look for those moments. They just happen. A lot of what you learn as you age you can just be boiled down to conserving your energy. You&rsquo;re too tired. Now, you&rsquo;re old. It&rsquo;s just not worth the time anymore. You can&rsquo;t force relationships. If it causes any stress, it&rsquo;s wasting my time. Time is money. Money is fun. Fun is distraction. You see how it all connects. Ironically being more relaxed about what you want will make it happen. More meaning if you want a relationship. For me the best example was how much I used to try to force relationships with my first girlfriend. We were inevitably going to break up. I could not let go of her. I knew it but I felt like the protagonist. I needed a romantic interest at this point in the life movie.</p>
<p>The brain is like a computer it needs something to do or else it&rsquo;s just gonna rot. Problems don&rsquo;t stop, they adjust. That&rsquo;s how it&rsquo;s gonna be for people like me. I bet you&rsquo;re the same with something to prove. Grown but time left on the clock. No matter how rich, famous, pretty, it&rsquo;s always going to be some problem. People can only retire and relax on a beach they&rsquo;re old because you don&rsquo;t have any other energy left. I&rsquo;m at this weird point where if I reach a light amount of success doing what I love doing. I can kind of coast in this comfort zone. If I stop now and settle, I&rsquo;m not a failure. But if I don&rsquo;t progress then I fall off which is worse than failing. This is such a good problem to have, but it&rsquo;s one of my hardest obstacles. At 19 you got to get of your head and look from a different perspective. You get older and see how selfish it is to ever think you&rsquo;re the main character. To ever think that your problems are the end of the world. You don&rsquo;t matter at this age. You can&rsquo;t hide behind the endearing youthfulness full of hope and possibility you&rsquo;re not cute anymore. You&rsquo;re turning 19, you&rsquo;re gonna be like this for a while.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>a tutorial</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/a-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/a-tutorial/</guid><description>./pre-nut I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to view women like most men. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard some negative feedback on my ability to co-exist with whiny overdramatic females properly. What sticks out to me, is that they spend so much effort on looking good but their biggest issue with us is our creepy male gaze. She just wants to feel pretty and you&amp;rsquo;re telling her cheesy pickup lines from google. It feels impossible to act normal around someone that&amp;rsquo;s literally carrying gold between their legs.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="pre-nut">./pre-nut</h1>
<p>I don&rsquo;t know how I&rsquo;m supposed to view women like most men. I&rsquo;ve heard some negative feedback on my ability to co-exist with whiny overdramatic females properly. What sticks out to me, is that they spend so much effort on looking good but their biggest issue with us is our creepy male gaze. She just wants to feel pretty and you&rsquo;re telling her cheesy pickup lines from google. It feels impossible to act normal around someone that&rsquo;s literally carrying gold between their legs. Even when she gets under your skin, what she got still feels worth it. You try to push away those feelings because when she realises your intention, she loses interest and kind of thinks you&rsquo;re pathetic. Your self-worth is dependent on her opinion and she starts resenting all the creepy jealous male anger that comes with it at some point. It&rsquo;s time to stop thinking like this. That&rsquo;s how the same woman who was pursued for her beauty ends up discarded and cut in half by some attractive guy. Maybe she can do more than spread her legs. Maybe if you look closer you&rsquo;ll see something you never noticed before. Maybe if you don&rsquo;t all the girls your age will have learned from their mistake and avoid some guy like you forever. But you also want to have the ability to sweep any girl off her feet, not in hopes that life is going to open the door for somebody better. Because you&rsquo;re insecure and women&rsquo;s admiration makes up for what you&rsquo;re lacking. It&rsquo;s selfish but you&rsquo;re tired of lifting women up on a pedestal only to doze off mid-conversation because you&rsquo;re talking to a girl who never had to develop a personality. Viewing women like romantic balls of joy is just as dumb as objectifying them because your heart will always get broken. Now, look at yourself. You&rsquo;re worried that if you keep viewing women as accessories for your life you will become a labeled incel. So it&rsquo;s time to go outside and meet real women platonic and celibate. I&rsquo;m going to do all the research I can on how to untoxify myself and figure out the right way to view women.</p>
<hr>
<h1 id="post-nut">./post-nut</h1>
<p>Every girl has a different answer I don&rsquo;t even think they know what they want to be viewed. They want you to be straightforward but not too straightforward. But not too straightforward creep. They want your attention but only at the perfect moment when they need it. They kind of expect you to know how to read their minds. I&rsquo;m starting to understand why a lot guys play it safe and stick to the hub. I&rsquo;m talking like this issue is universal. I attach so much importance to women&rsquo;s attention because I grew up not knowing how to socialise. When you can&rsquo;t get something, you start believing you won&rsquo;t be happy until you do. Your value as a man shouldn&rsquo;t depend on a woman. She simply wants somebody that doesn&rsquo;t need her instead. Instead of approaching women as a projection of your desires. It&rsquo;s better to see them as just other people. Usually, people are more interesting than they seem.</p>
<hr>
<h3 id="afterword">./afterword</h3>
<blockquote>
<p><code>I'm not an incel. I'm not this toxic person that I display here. Well I used to be. Very obviously put on in the beginning so that I can debunk an argument at the end. The misogyny that I'm trying to debunk is the whole part was trying to come off like a misogynist person. I'm taking a perspective of a neurotic and angst man who doesn't know how to communicate. Knowing so many men who are like this, there's a bit of irony that I'm trying to convey a nuanced perspective to be truthful. If you want to say something controversial and telling and say what you really feel, you're going to risk having people canceling you. That is called growth.</code></p>
</blockquote>
<p><em>~ inspired by she tyler the creator</em></p>
]]></content></item><item><title>the stage is yours</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/the-stage-is-yours/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/the-stage-is-yours/</guid><description>Social media has completely taken over our lives to the point where it&amp;rsquo;s a second reality.
It&amp;rsquo;s all a performance.
No other generation has to pretend to know what they&amp;rsquo;re talking about. Today our entertainment is people&amp;rsquo;s lives. Where attention is literally a currency. I understand trying to take accountabiliy for your actions but everyone&amp;rsquo;s trying so hard to be on the right side of history that they sound like robots.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Social media has completely taken over our lives to the point where it&rsquo;s a second reality.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>It&rsquo;s all a performance.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>No other generation has to pretend to know what they&rsquo;re talking about. Today our entertainment is people&rsquo;s lives. Where attention is literally a currency. I understand trying to take accountabiliy for your actions but everyone&rsquo;s trying so hard to be on the right side of history that they sound like robots. Deciding what is right from wrong. They only do it to appear morally superior to people online.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve realised being away from people how much I missed it. When you speak to someone face to face, suddenly all that noise you forget about when you&rsquo;re in the real world talking to real people. People drop their act when you talk to them face to face. I&rsquo;ve realised how much I say in conversations not because it&rsquo;s truthful or it&rsquo;s funny but because how people are going to perceive me if I tell them. We want to seem special. We want to be cooler than we really are. But you&rsquo;ll notice as soon as you say something embarassing. As soon as you actually open up to someone. Their guard goes away. Now they&rsquo;re not performing. You can speak to them like they really are. When in reality, I&rsquo;m guilty of all the stuff I&rsquo;m criticising. I&rsquo;m completely addicted to social media. And I care too much what people think about me.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>for her</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/for-her/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/for-her/</guid><description>The dilemma for me was deciding when the stress of a relationship outweighs the love. How do you know when you&amp;rsquo;re just better off by yourself?
I learned the answer is success just has no time for emotions. People get on top of any industry by working algorithmically. But most likely you&amp;rsquo;re like me where horny and lonely is enough to pause your whole life. The reason I made this, is it forces me to reflect and be objective with my first relationship instead of being petty.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The dilemma for me was deciding when the stress of a relationship outweighs the love. How do you know when you&rsquo;re just better off by yourself?</p>
<p>I learned the answer is success just has no time for emotions. People get on top of any industry by working algorithmically. But most likely you&rsquo;re like me where horny and lonely is enough to pause your whole life. The reason I made this, is it forces me to reflect and be objective with my first relationship instead of being petty. What I really want to do is villianize her in my head and fixate on all the bad things, yet the reality is I was closer with her than I was with any other human in that time period. I travelled with her, pillow talked every night, matured and learned about each other. Now we don&rsquo;t even speak. I know our experiences will stay with me forever and that&rsquo;s the part I should remember.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em><strong>My chapter with her is now over and it was a good one.</strong></em></p>
</blockquote>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>