<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on ze sheng</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on ze sheng</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright/><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zes1092.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>law and order</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/law-and-order/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/law-and-order/</guid><description>The people who are dependent on the system will fight and defend the system
The whole idea of law and order is a constructed lie. All it is, is about if you are high enough of this ladder. Law is just a purposefully ambiguous and confusing language just for higher powers. They benefit by exercising their power just to enslave the lower filfth. As Orwellian beautifully hypothesised &amp;ldquo;War is Peace, Freedom is Slavery, Ignorance is Strength&amp;rdquo;.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>The people who are dependent on the system will fight and defend the system</p>
</blockquote>
<p>The whole idea of law and order is a constructed lie. All it is, is about if you are high enough of this ladder. Law is just a purposefully ambiguous and confusing language just for higher powers. They benefit by exercising their power just to enslave the lower filfth. As Orwellian beautifully hypothesised &ldquo;War is Peace, Freedom is Slavery, Ignorance is Strength&rdquo;. Numbed to our core, distracted with first world problems that we may as well believe &ldquo;2 + 2 = 5&rdquo;.</p>
<p>Corruption exists everywhere but operates on a different level in the western world. Nothing left besides money and corporate agenda. Where there is no moral fiber beyond the dollar. I find it offensive that corruption is not accessible for everybody. If certain higher identities can play the game, let us all play.</p>
<p>To ever believe that the government is the guardian of democracy is impossible. Yet, governments still fail to do the principal baseline. The NSW Premier, Gladys is by far the personification of the unseen monolith cunt by enforcing compulsory mandates such as lockdowns and vaccinations. Gladys now pulls a clueless face on what has happened. Leads a whole generation into further recession. Refuses to elaborate. Gets strangled by her own set of orders. All for what. Just to comply with pointless health guidelines. All because 98% of Covid-19 deaths were because of people with a low immune system or had some serious underlying health condition.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>If I do reach that status of higher power, I will reap all of the benefits of corruption. At that point, I will blindly rip an eye out for the government. I will fuck the government.</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content></item><item><title>must be projection</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/must-be-projection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/must-be-projection/</guid><description>I always wonder why people who’ve accomplished nothing in their life feel so comfortable talking down to me. must be projection. talking about your personal accomplishments openly isn’t arrogant. It just makes people who don’t do shit feel bad. that’s their problem.</description><content type="html">&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I always wonder why people who’ve accomplished nothing in their life feel so comfortable talking down to me. must be projection. talking about your personal accomplishments openly isn’t arrogant. It just makes people who don’t do shit feel bad. that’s their problem.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></content></item><item><title>fuckery</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/fuckery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/fuckery/</guid><description>For most of human history, we lived in small, tight knit communities where everybody knew everything about everyone else. Being seen and understood wasn’t an issue. Now we live in a world of strangers, where attention spans are short, and loneliness is endemic. Depth and complexity are liabilities: digestibility is key. You compress your personality into something which people can grasp in 10 seconds or less, before they get bored and swipe you away into oblivion.</description><content type="html">&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>For most of human history, we lived in small, tight knit communities where everybody knew everything about everyone else. Being seen and understood wasn’t an issue. Now we live in a world of strangers, where attention spans are short, and loneliness is endemic. Depth and complexity are liabilities: digestibility is key. You compress your personality into something which people can grasp in 10 seconds or less, before they get bored and swipe you away into oblivion. Something which they cannot ignore, even if it means making yourself into a human car wreck. Tiktok is the kabuki theatre of compressed personalities. People behave like caricatures of themselves, or who they wish to be. The proliferation of subcultures (alt-tiktok, emo-tiktok, cottagecore-tiktok) further flattens them into premade archetypes based around consumption patterns. You find the box which fits best, squeeze inside, and hope someone will love you. An act of self-dehumanization which provokes a natural response of cringe.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></content></item><item><title>linger</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/linger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/linger/</guid><description>For some time, it&amp;rsquo;s been understood that moderate stress has beneficial effects. For example, it stimulates the immune system. As they say, it serves motivation in life. You could even call it a reason for living. However, once overstimulation checks became routine, people have found their sense of stress numbed so heavily that we started to see patients who couldn&amp;rsquo;t even recognise stimulation itself. Once that happens, they&amp;rsquo;re like living corpses.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For some time, it&rsquo;s been understood that moderate stress has beneficial effects. For example, it stimulates the immune system. As they say, it serves motivation in life. You could even call it a reason for living. However, once overstimulation checks became routine, people have found their sense of stress numbed so heavily that we started to see patients who couldn&rsquo;t even recognise stimulation itself. Once that happens, they&rsquo;re like living corpses. Soon their autonomic nervous system stops functioning on its own and their vital functions shut down. Humans now care themselves to the point that they&rsquo;ve actually regressed as living beings. As much as our medical system has advanced, statistically the diagnosis of mental illness is actually increasing. This data will probably never be made public, though. Everything that could be considered a reason to live had died out. No one tries to talk seriously about what life should be like anymore.</p>
<p>Ouryou Rouichi, possessed a prodigious talent for drawing cruel, vivid nightmares using girls&rsquo; bodies as motifs. However, himself was a man of quite strict morality. It&rsquo;s not uncommon for there to be a disconnect between the creator and their impression their creators give. But in Rouichi&rsquo;s case, there was firm ideology there. According to him, by becoming firmly aware of the cruelty that hides in the dark depths of the human heart, humans can foster the common sense, ability to reason and goodwill to control that cruelty. He viewed his creative efforts as a means to englighten the populace. However, the spread of online recognition, ended this role that he had decided for himself. People don&rsquo;t have to control themselves anymore. Instead, they can now mainttain their mental health through machine assessments. Whatever the means, his ideal of humanity having healthy and sound minds had been realised. As a result, though, his mission ended and his life lost its meaning. With artists, concerned only with fame and wealth, he too probably had inner conflicts. In order to solve them, he used all kinds of state-of-the-art stress care methods. He was so dependent on them that you could call it addiction. Became a living corpse who couldn&rsquo;t get up in his own bed. It&rsquo;s as if Ouryou Rouichi was killed twice. First, his talent was killed by science and technology. And then, his soul was killed by society.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>finger me</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/finger-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/finger-me/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m turning 19 this summer. I&amp;rsquo;m at the age where you stop living in your own personal movie starring you. Reality is too much to pretend like everyone gets a happy ending. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how distraction is necessary doing mindless activities like shopping and partying will keep you sane a little bit longer. 16 year old fake deep me would look at people in the mall like look at all these NPC.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m turning 19 this summer. I&rsquo;m at the age where you stop living in your own personal movie starring you. Reality is too much to pretend like everyone gets a happy ending. I&rsquo;ve learned how <strong>distraction is necessary</strong> doing mindless activities like shopping and partying will keep you sane a little bit longer. 16 year old fake deep me would look at people in the mall like look at all these NPC. I looked down at people numbing themselves with plastic because they didn&rsquo;t realise how pointless it was. Now I&rsquo;m like everyone knows we&rsquo;re all just trying to distract ourselves for a bit because life sucks and its draining. I used to be entitled thinking that I was unique for overthinking every situation all the time like life always had to be filled with act 3 movie scenes with dramatic realisations but you can&rsquo;t look for those moments. They just happen. A lot of what you learn as you age you can just be boiled down to conserving your energy. You&rsquo;re too tired. Now, you&rsquo;re old. It&rsquo;s just not worth the time anymore. You can&rsquo;t force relationships. If it causes any stress, it&rsquo;s wasting my time. Time is money. Money is fun. Fun is distraction. You see how it all connects. Ironically being more relaxed about what you want will make it happen. More meaning if you want a relationship. For me the best example was how much I used to try to force relationships with my first girlfriend. We were inevitably going to break up. I could not let go of her. I knew it but I felt like the protagonist. I needed a romantic interest at this point in the life movie.</p>
<p>The brain is like a computer it needs something to do or else it&rsquo;s just gonna rot. Problems don&rsquo;t stop, they adjust. That&rsquo;s how it&rsquo;s gonna be for people like me. I bet you&rsquo;re the same with something to prove. Grown but time left on the clock. No matter how rich, famous, pretty, it&rsquo;s always going to be some problem. People can only retire and relax on a beach they&rsquo;re old because you don&rsquo;t have any other energy left. I&rsquo;m at this weird point where if I reach a light amount of success doing what I love doing. I can kind of coast in this comfort zone. If I stop now and settle, I&rsquo;m not a failure. But if I don&rsquo;t progress then I fall off which is worse than failing. This is such a good problem to have, but it&rsquo;s one of my hardest obstacles. At 19 you got to get of your head and look from a different perspective. You get older and see how selfish it is to ever think you&rsquo;re the main character. To ever think that your problems are the end of the world. You don&rsquo;t matter at this age. You can&rsquo;t hide behind the endearing youthfulness full of hope and possibility you&rsquo;re not cute anymore. You&rsquo;re turning 19, you&rsquo;re gonna be like this for a while.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>a tutorial</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/a-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/a-tutorial/</guid><description>pre nut I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to view women like most men. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard some negative feedback on my ability to co-exist with whiny overdramatic females properly. What sticks out to me, is that they spend so much effort on looking good but their biggest issue with us is our creepy male gaze. She just wants to feel pretty and you&amp;rsquo;re telling her cheesy pickup lines from google. It feels impossible to act normal around someone that&amp;rsquo;s literally carrying gold between their legs.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="pre-nut">pre nut</h2>
<p>I don&rsquo;t know how I&rsquo;m supposed to view women like most men. I&rsquo;ve heard some negative feedback on my ability to co-exist with whiny overdramatic females properly. What sticks out to me, is that they spend so much effort on looking good but their biggest issue with us is our creepy male gaze. She just wants to feel pretty and you&rsquo;re telling her cheesy pickup lines from google. It feels impossible to act normal around someone that&rsquo;s literally carrying gold between their legs. Even when she gets under your skin, what she got still feels worth it. You try to push away those feelings because when she realises your intention, she loses interest and kind of thinks you&rsquo;re pathetic. Your self-worth is dependent on her opinion and she starts resenting all the creepy jealous male anger that comes with it at some point. It&rsquo;s time to stop thinking like this. That&rsquo;s how the same woman who was pursued for her beauty ends up discarded and cut in half by some attractive guy. Maybe she can do more than spread her legs. Maybe if you look closer you&rsquo;ll see something you never noticed before. Maybe if you don&rsquo;t all the girls your age will have learned from their mistake and avoid some guy like you forever. But you also want to have the ability to sweep any girl off her feet, not in hopes that life is going to open the door for somebody better. Because you&rsquo;re insecure and women&rsquo;s admiration makes up for what you&rsquo;re lacking. It&rsquo;s selfish but you&rsquo;re tired of lifting women up on a pedestal only to doze off mid-conversation because you&rsquo;re talking to a girl who never had to develop a personality. Viewing women like romantic balls of joy is just as dumb as objectifying them because your heart will always get broken. Now, look at yourself. You&rsquo;re worried that if you keep viewing women as accessories for your life you will become a labeled incel. So it&rsquo;s time to go outside and meet real women platonic and celibate. I&rsquo;m going to do all the research I can on how to untoxify myself and figure out the right way to view women.</p>
<hr>
<h2 id="post-nut">post nut</h2>
<p>Every girl has a different answer I don&rsquo;t even think they know what they want to be viewed. They want you to be straightforward but not too straightforward. But not too straightforward creep. They want your attention but only at the perfect moment when they need it. They kind of expect you to know how to read their minds. I&rsquo;m starting to understand why a lot guys play it safe and stick to the hub. I&rsquo;m talking like this issue is universal. I attach so much importance to women&rsquo;s attention because I grew up not knowing how to socialise. When you can&rsquo;t get something, you start believing you won&rsquo;t be happy until you do. Your value as a man shouldn&rsquo;t depend on a woman. She simply wants somebody that doesn&rsquo;t need her instead. Instead of approaching women as a projection of your desires. It&rsquo;s better to see them as just other people. Usually, people are more interesting than they seem.</p>
<hr>
<h3 id="clarity">clarity</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>I&rsquo;m not an incel. I&rsquo;m not this toxic person that I display here. Well I used to be. Very obviously put on in the beginning so that I can debunk an argument at the end. The misogyny that I&rsquo;m trying to debunk is the whole part was trying to come off like a misogynist person. I&rsquo;m taking a perspective of a neurotic and angst man who doesn&rsquo;t know how to communicate. Knowing so many men who are like this, there&rsquo;s a bit of irony that I&rsquo;m trying to convey a nuanced perspective to be truthful. If you want to say something controversial and telling and say what you really feel, you&rsquo;re going to risk having people canceling you. That is called growth.</p>
</blockquote>
<blockquote>
<p>~ inspired by she tyler the creator</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content></item><item><title>fifteen million merits</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/fifteen-million-merits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/fifteen-million-merits/</guid><description>I haven’t got a speech, I didn’t plan words, I didn’t even try to. I just knew that I had to get here, to stand here and I knew I wanted you to listen; to really listen, not just pull a face like you’re listening, like you do the rest of the time. A face like you’re feeling instead of processing. You pull a face and poke it towards the stage and la-di-da we sing and dance and tumble around and all you see up here, it’s not people, you don’t see people up here, it’s all fodder.</description><content type="html">&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>I haven’t got a speech, I didn’t plan words, I didn’t even try to. I just knew that I had to get here, to stand here and I knew I wanted you to listen; to really listen, not just pull a face like you’re listening, like you do the rest of the time. A face like you’re feeling instead of processing. You pull a face and poke it towards the stage and la-di-da we sing and dance and tumble around and all you see up here, it’s not people, you don’t see people up here, it’s all fodder. And the faker the fodder is the more you love it because fake fodder’s the only thing that works anymore, fake fodder is all that we can stomach — actually not quite all. Real pain, real viciousness, that we can take. Yeah, stick a fat man up a pole and we’ll laugh ourselves feral cause we’ve earned the right, we’ve done cell time and he’s slacking the scum so ha ha ha at him. Cause we’re so out of our minds with desperation we don’t know any better. All we know is fake fodder and buying shit. That’s how we speak to each other, how we express ourselves is buying shit. I have a dream? The peak of our dreams is a new hat for our doppel, a hat that doesn’t exist. It’s not even there, we buy shit that’s not even there. Show us something real and free and beautiful, you couldn’t. It’d break us, we’re too numb for it, our minds would choke. There’s only so much wonder we can bear, that’s why when you find any wonder whatsoever you dole it out in meager portions, and only then til it’s augmented and packaged and pumped through ten thousand pre-assigned filters, til it’s nothing more than a meaningless series of lights, while we ride day-in, day-out — going where? Powering what? All tiny cells in tiny screens and bigger cells in bigger screens and fuck you. Fuck you, that’s what it boils down to is fuck you. Fuck you for sitting there and slowly knitting things worse. Fuck you and your spotlight and your sanctimonious faces and fuck you all, for taking the one thing I ever came close to anything real about anything. For oozing around it and crushing it into a bone, into a joke, one more ugly joke in a kingdom of millions and then fuck you. Fuck you for happening. Fuck you for me, for us, for everyone, fuck you&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></content></item><item><title>the stage is yours</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/the-stage-is-yours/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/the-stage-is-yours/</guid><description>Social media has completely taken over our lives to the point where it&amp;rsquo;s a second reality.
It&amp;rsquo;s all a performance.
No other generation has to pretend to know what they&amp;rsquo;re talking about. Today our entertainment is people&amp;rsquo;s lives. Where attention is literally a currency. I understand trying to take accountabiliy for your actions but everyone&amp;rsquo;s trying so hard to be on the right side of history that they sound like robots.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Social media has completely taken over our lives to the point where it&rsquo;s a second reality.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>It&rsquo;s all a performance.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>No other generation has to pretend to know what they&rsquo;re talking about. Today our entertainment is people&rsquo;s lives. Where attention is literally a currency. I understand trying to take accountabiliy for your actions but everyone&rsquo;s trying so hard to be on the right side of history that they sound like robots. Deciding what is right from wrong. They only do it to appear morally superior to people online.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve realised being away from people how much I missed it. When you speak to someone face to face, suddenly all that noise you forget about when you&rsquo;re in the real world talking to real people. People drop their act when you talk to them face to face. I&rsquo;ve realised how much I say in conversations not because it&rsquo;s truthful or it&rsquo;s funny but because how people are going to perceive me if I tell them. We want to seem special. We want to be cooler than we really are. But you&rsquo;ll notice as soon as you say something embarassing. As soon as you actually open up to someone. Their guard goes away. Now they&rsquo;re not performing. You can speak to them like they really are. When in reality, I&rsquo;m guilty of all the stuff I&rsquo;m criticising. I&rsquo;m completely addicted to social media. And I care too much what people think about me.</p>
]]></content></item><item><title>157cm</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/157cm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/157cm/</guid><description>The dilemma for me was deciding when the stress of a relationship outweighs the love. How do you know when you&amp;rsquo;re just better off by yourself?
I learned the answer is success just has no time for emotions. People get on top of any industry by working algorithmically. But most likely you&amp;rsquo;re like me where horny and lonely is enough to pause your whole life. The reason I made this, is it forces me to reflect and be objective with my first relationship instead of being petty.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The dilemma for me was deciding when the stress of a relationship outweighs the love. How do you know when you&rsquo;re just better off by yourself?</p>
<p>I learned the answer is success just has no time for emotions. People get on top of any industry by working algorithmically. But most likely you&rsquo;re like me where horny and lonely is enough to pause your whole life. The reason I made this, is it forces me to reflect and be objective with my first relationship instead of being petty. What I really want to do is villianize her in my head and fixate on all the bad things, yet the reality is I was closer with her than I was with any other human in that time period. I travelled with her, pillow talked every night, matured and learned about each other. Now we don&rsquo;t even speak. I know our experiences will stay with me forever and that&rsquo;s the part I should remember.</p>
<blockquote>
<p><em><strong>My chapter with her is now over and it was a good one.</strong></em></p>
</blockquote>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>