<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>algos on ze sheng</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/series/algos/</link><description>Recent content in algos on ze sheng</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright/><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zes1092.github.io/series/algos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>fuckery</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/fuckery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/fuckery/</guid><description>For most of human history, we lived in small, tight knit communities where everybody knew everything about everyone else. Being seen and understood wasn’t an issue. Now we live in a world of strangers, where attention spans are short, and loneliness is endemic. Depth and complexity are liabilities: digestibility is key. You compress your personality into something which people can grasp in 10 seconds or less, before they get bored and swipe you away into oblivion.</description></item><item><title>linger</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/linger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/linger/</guid><description>For some time, it&amp;rsquo;s been understood that moderate stress has beneficial effects. For example, it stimulates the immune system. As they say, it serves motivation in life. You could even call it a reason for living. However, once overstimulation checks became routine, people have found their sense of stress numbed so heavily that we started to see patients who couldn&amp;rsquo;t even recognise stimulation itself. Once that happens, they&amp;rsquo;re like living corpses.</description></item><item><title>finger me</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/finger-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/finger-me/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m turning 19 this summer. I&amp;rsquo;m at the age where you stop living in your own personal movie starring you. Reality is too much to pretend like everyone gets a happy ending. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned how distraction is necessary doing mindless activities like shopping and partying will keep you sane a little bit longer. 16 year old fake deep me would look at people in the mall like look at all these NPC.</description></item><item><title>a tutorial</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/a-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/a-tutorial/</guid><description>pre nut I don&amp;rsquo;t know how I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to view women like most men. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard some negative feedback on my ability to co-exist with whiny overdramatic females properly. What sticks out to me, is that they spend so much effort on looking good but their biggest issue with us is our creepy male gaze. She just wants to feel pretty and you&amp;rsquo;re telling her cheesy pickup lines from google. It feels impossible to act normal around someone that&amp;rsquo;s literally carrying gold between their legs.</description></item><item><title>the stage is yours</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/the-stage-is-yours/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/the-stage-is-yours/</guid><description>Social media has completely taken over our lives to the point where it&amp;rsquo;s a second reality.
It&amp;rsquo;s all a performance.
No other generation has to pretend to know what they&amp;rsquo;re talking about. Today our entertainment is people&amp;rsquo;s lives. Where attention is literally a currency. I understand trying to take accountabiliy for your actions but everyone&amp;rsquo;s trying so hard to be on the right side of history that they sound like robots.</description></item><item><title>157cm</title><link>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/157cm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zes1092.github.io/posts/157cm/</guid><description>The dilemma for me was deciding when the stress of a relationship outweighs the love. How do you know when you&amp;rsquo;re just better off by yourself?
I learned the answer is success just has no time for emotions. People get on top of any industry by working algorithmically. But most likely you&amp;rsquo;re like me where horny and lonely is enough to pause your whole life. The reason I made this, is it forces me to reflect and be objective with my first relationship instead of being petty.</description></item></channel></rss>